One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
What's wrong, Zoro?
ما خطبك يا زورو؟
You've had a serious look on your face for a while.
يعلو وجهك تعبيرٌ جادٌ منذ فترة
Well, I might just be imagining things, but...
...حسنٌ... آمل أنّ هذا من وحي خيالي، ولكن
But what?
لكن ماذا؟
I feel like the ship hasn't moved in a while.
أشعر أنّ السفينة لم تتحرك منذ مدة
What?
ماذا؟
Now that you mention it, the sail isn't catching any wind...
على ذِكر ذلك، لم تهبّ أيّ رياح على الشراع
Oh no...!
!تبًّا
We've entered the Calm Belt!
!دخلنا الحزام الهادئ
The Balm Belt?
الحزام الهاذي؟
The heck is that?
ما هذا؟
The Calm Belt! A sea where nothing moves a muscle!
الحزام الهادئ! إنه بحرٌ يغمره السُّكون
You grew some muscle?
تلاعب لفظي من لوفي
No, you idiot!
!أحمق
Was that an earthquake?
ما الخطب؟ أهذا زلزال؟
An earthquake? But we're at sea.
زلزال؟ ولكننا على البحر
Come on, guys, focus!
!كفاكُم حديثًا
Hoist the sails and start paddling!
!اربطوا الأشرعة وابدؤوا التجديف
Put the ship back on course, now!
!أعيدونا إلى مسارنا السابق
As you wish, Nami!
!حاضر يا نامي-سان
What are you panicking about?
لماذا أنتِ مذعورة؟
And why paddle? This is a sailboat.
هذه سفينة شراعية، كيف سنجدف بها؟
Yeah, why?
صحيح
Just shut up and do as I say! We're in big trouble!
افعلوا ما أقوله فحسب! إنّنا في ورطة
But the sea is nice and quiet here.
ولكن البحرَ هادئ
Yeah.
أجل
Alright, fine! I'll explain!
يا إلهي! طيب، سأشرح لكم
Listen. Since we were in such a hurry, we went farther south than intended!
اسمعوا، بما أننا هربنا على عجل فقد اتجهنا جنوبًا أكثر مما خططنا
So we're in the Grand Line now?
أنحنٌ في الغراند لاين إذًا؟
Alright!
!وأخيرًا
If it was that easy, anyone could enter!
لو كان دخوله بهذه البساطة، لدخله أيّ أحد
Look here.
انظروا
The Grand Line runs between these two strips of sea.
تقع وجهتنا الغراند لاين بين منطقتين بحريّتين
Are you following? The two strips are called the Calm Belts.
أفهمتم؟ ما يُحيط به من الجانبين يُعرَف بالحزام الهادئ
The reason's unknown, but no wind or currents flow through them.
إنّه يخلو من الرياح والتيارات، ولا يُعرَف السبب
These seas are completely calm.
إنها منطقة بحرية ساكنة تمامًا
Sailboats need wind to move so it's very dangerous—
السفن الشراعية لا تتحرك من دون رياح، لذا فالوضع خطير
maybe even fatal—without it!
وكأنها منطقة مميتة لها
Did you get all that, Luffy?
أفهمتَ يا لوفي؟
Yeah. Basically, we're in trouble.
أجل. فهمتُ أنّنا في ورطة
That explains the lack of wind.
هذا يُفسّر انعدام الرياح
Not much we can do if the ship can't move.
لا حيلة لنا إن لم تتحرّك السفينة
Can't we just wait for wind to–
علينا انتظار هبوب الرياح
I just explained this! Wind won't blow no matter how long you wait here!
ألم أشرح ذلك توًّا؟ لن تهبّ الرياح مهما انتظرنا
And that's not all!
وليس هذا فحسب
There's another reason this area is dangerous!
ثمّة سبب آخر يجعل هذه المنطقة خطيرة
The Calm Belt is–
...إن الحزام الهادئ
What's going on?
!ما الذي يحدث؟
They're here!
!ها هم
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Th-Th-They're...
...إ-إ-إنهم
They're huge!
!ضِخام
The Calm Belt is a nest of sea kings.
،إن الحزام الهادئ وكر ملوك البحر
Specifically colossal ones.
وخاصةً الضخام منهم
They're the other reason people can't cross the Calm Belt...
وجودهم هو السبب الآخر لتجنّب الناس الحزام الهادئ
What do we do now?
ماذا سنفعل الآن؟
F-For the time being, no one move.
فـ-في الوقت الراهن، لا تتحرّكوا
They'll go back into the sea eventually.
ستعود إلى البحر تدريجيًا على الأرجح
When they do, we paddle as hard as possible.
ومن ثم سنجدف بكل قوتنا
Are you serious?!
!هل أنت جاد؟
Shut it, idiot!
!أحمق
Sorry...
...المعذرة
Hold on a sec...!
...تمهّل
If it does that...
...إن فعلها
He's gonna sneeze!
!فسيعطس
– What?!
!ماذا؟
Wow! It feels like we're flying!
!مذهل! وكأنّنا نطير
We are flying!
!إنّنا نطير فعلًا
Looks like we're back on course...
يبدو أنّنا عُدنا إلى مسارنا الصحيح
We should be seeing the Red Line any moment now.
سنرى الريد لاين في أيّ لحظة
Are we finally going into the Grand Line?!
!سنصل إلى الغراند لاين أخيرًا
Hey, Sanji! We're here, we're here, we're finally here!
!يا سانجي! سنصل أخيرًا! أخيرًا، أخيرًا
That hurts!
!هذا مؤلم
Sorry...
أعتذر
Zoro!
!زورو
We're here, we're here!
!سنصل، سنصل
But...
...لكن
We're here, we're here, we're here!
!سنصل، سنصل، سنصل
is the drawing an accurate representation of what we'll find?
أتمثّل الرسمة ما سنراه فعلًا؟
Quit it!
!كفى
Look at this!
!انظروا لهذه
I'd heard the rumors about it, and it's drawn on this map, too!
سمعتُ إشاعاتٍ عديدة، وقد رُسم في هذه الخريطة كذلك
If all of that is true, then the entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain!
!فإن صحّت الإشاعات، فمدخل الغراند لاين جبل
A mountain?
جبل؟
We gotta crash into it?
!سنصطدم بجبل؟
You're kidding, right?
لا يُعقَل
I doubted it myself, but the map shows canals leading to the mountain.
راودني الشكّ، لكن الخريطة تُظهر قنواتٍ تؤدّي إلى جبل
That might mean we have to go up it!
!ولعلّ علينا صعوده
Cool!
!مثير
What are you talking about?!
!ماذا تقول؟
Even with canals or whatever, a ship can't climb up a mountain!
!مهما كانت تلك القنوات فالسفينة محالٌ عليها صعود الجبال
But that's what the map says!
!هذا ما تُظهره الخريطة
Exactly! Nami would never say anything wrong!
!أجل، نامي-سان لا تنطق إلا صوابًا
You stole that map from Buggy, right?
سرقتِ هذه الخريطة من باغي، صحيح؟
Can we really trust it?
أيمكننا الوثوق بها؟
H-Hey!
!أ-أنتم
Someone help me move the whipstaff!
!فليساعدني أحدٌ في الدفة
Sanji! Give Usopp a hand!
ساعد أوسوب يا سانجي-كن
I can't think with all his shouting!
ضجّته تمنعني من التفكير
Right away, Nami!
!حاضر يا نامي-سان
Here I go!
هيّا
It won't budge!
!إنّه لا يتحرك
It won't move! Someone help!
!إنّه لا يتحرك، فليساعدني أحد
D-Doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!
!أ-ألا يبدو هذا التيّار قويًّا؟
Usopp, say that again!
ماذا قلت توًّا يا أوسوب؟
"D-Doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!"
!أ-ألا يبدو هذا التيار قويًّا؟
Current...
...تيّار
That's it!
!فهمت
What's it?
ماذا؟
The canals do go up the mountain!
!علينا صعود الجبال حقًّا
You're still on that?
أما زلتِ تصرينَ على ذلك؟
Look here!
!انظروا هنا
See?
،اصغوا بتمعّن
The guiding light was definitely pointing to here.
هنا كان يشير الضوء المُرشد
Right on the Red Line: Reverse Mountain!
!الجبل المعكوس الموجود في الريد لاين
Hey! What do I do now?!
أنتم! ماذا أفعل بهذه؟
See these canals here?
توجد قنوات هنا، أليس كذلك؟
If major currents from the four seas all flowed toward this mountain...
،إن كانت كلّ التيارات الكبرى من البحار الأربعة تتدفق نحو هذا الجبل
Then the four currents would go up these canals, collide at the top,
فإنّ هذه التيارات الأربعة ستصعد إلى أعلى هذه القنوات وتصطدم عاليًا
and flow into the Grand Line!
!ومن ثم تتدفّق إلى الغراند لاين
Reverse Mountain is a winter island,
،بما أن الجبل المعكوس جزيرة شتائيّة
so any currents that collide with the Red Line will go into the depths.
لذا فإنَّ أيّ تيارٍ يرتطم بالريد لاين سينحدر إلى الأعماق
If we screw up and miss the entrance to the canal...
،إن أخطأنا وضيّعنا مدخل القناة
the Going Merry will crash into the Red Line...
...فإنّ غوينغ ميري ستصطدم مباشرةً بالريد لاين
and get completely wrecked!
!وتتحطّم
Then we'd end up at the bottom of the ocean. Get it?
وسنكون حينها في قاع البحر. أفهمتم؟
Oh, very interesting!
!هكذا إذًا
So, basically, it's a mystery mountain!
!باختصار، إنّه جبلٌ غامض
Well, I guess you wouldn't...
...توقعت ألّا تفهم
All in all, now that we're on this current,
،على أيّ حال، ما دُمنا فوق هذا التيار
as long as we steer correctly,
وما دمنا لم نُخطئ في توجيه الدفة
it's a straight shot to the summit of Reverse Mountain!
!فسنتمكّن من الوصول إلى قمة الجبل المعكوس مباشرةً
You're amazing, Nami!
!إنّكِ مذهلة يا نامي-سان
I've never heard of someone going up a mountain by boat.
لم أسمع بسفنٍ تصعدُ جبالًا من قبل
I've heard some stories!
أمّا أنا فقد سمعت البعض
About the mystery mountain?
قصصًا عن الجبل الغامض؟
No.
كلّا
I heard that half of everyone who heads to the Grand Line die before entering...
سمعتُ أنّ نصف من يتوجّهون إلى الغراند لاين يلقون حتفهم قبل بلوغه
I knew getting in wouldn't be easy.
كنتُ أعلم أنّ دخوله لن يكون سهلًا
Sanji! Could you get the sail?
تولَّ أمر الشراع يا سانجي-كن
Of course, Nami!
!حاضر يا نامي-سان
Luffy! Help out!
ساعدني يا لوفي
Hey!
!يا رفاق
I see the mystery mountain!
!أرى الجبل الغامض
– Wh-What?! – What?!
ماذا؟
Th-That's insanely huge!
!إ-إنّه ضخمٌ جدًّا
So that's the Red Line, huh?!
أهذا هو الريد لاين؟
Th-Th-The t-top's all the way above the clouds!
!لـ-لـ-لا أرى القمّة بسبب الغيوم
We're getting sucked in!
!سيسحبنا
Hold the rudder tight!
أمسكوا الدفة جيّدًا
– On it!
اعتمد علينا
N-Nami! Wh-Where's the entrance?!
!نـ-نامي! أين المدخل؟
We're gonna crash if we keep going this way!
!سنصطدم بالصخور إن واصلنا بهذا الاتجاه
The crack in that cliff...
...الصدع في ذلك الجرف
Nami! What do we do?!
!نامي! ماذا نفعل؟
Keep going straight ahead!
!استمرّا في التقدّم
Are you sure?!
!هل أنتِ جادّة؟
Just do it!
لا عليكم
Nami! Is that the entrance?
أذاك المدخل يا نامي؟
Most likely!
على الأرجح
I can't believe this...!
!لا أصدّق هذا
The damn ocean really is flowing up the mountain!
!يتدفّق البحر إلى أعلى الجبل فعلًا
We gotta be careful sailing through those gates!
،علينا أن نعبر هذه البوابات بسلاسة
If we don't get it just right, the ship is done for!
!وإلّا ستتحطّم السفينة إلى أشلاء
W-We're a little off! More to the right! The right!
!إ-إننا ننحرف عن مسارنا !إلى اليمين أكثر! اليمين، اليمين
The right?! Go starboard!
!اليمين؟! إلى الميمنة
C-Come on, now!
تمهلّوا
– The whipstaff!
!الدفة
Gum-Gum Balloon!
فاكهة المطّاط
Luffy!
!لوفي
Grab on!
أمسك بي
– We made it!
!نجحنا
Now it's just a straight shot to the summit!
!والآن، إلى القمّة مباشرةً
A-Awesome!
!مـ-مذهل
Awesome, right?
مذهل، أليس كذلك؟
We're in the clouds!
!إنّنا داخل الغيوم
So cool!
!مذهل
Now we're above the clouds!
!إنّنا فوق الغيوم الآن
Look! It's the summit! The summit!
!انظروا! القمّة، إنّها القمّة
Yahoo!
!مرحى
I see it!
...رأيتُه
This is the greatest sea in the world!
...أعظم بحار العالم
The Grand Line!
!الغراند لاين
The One Piece is somewhere up ahead!
!الون بيس موجودٌ في مكانٍ ما أمامنا
Go!
!انطلاق
Did you hear that just now?
أسمعتم شيئًا توًّا؟
Wasn't it just the wind?
أليست رياحًا فحسب؟
It must be from all the weird landforms around here.
لا بد من وجود تضاريس غير عادية
What's that?
ما هذا؟
Nami! I see a mountain up ahead!
!نامي-سان! أرى جبلًا أمامنا
A mountain?! That can't be right!
!جبل؟! هذا مستحيل
But there's really one there!
!لكنّه أمامنا فعلًا
Who cares?! Go!
!من يهتم؟! لننطلق
It should be open sea once we pass the Twin Capes up ahead!
بعدَ تجاوزِنا الرَّأسين التوأم لا ينبغي أن يعترضنا شيء
Oh, crap!
!مصيبة
It's not a mountain!
!لم يكن جبلًا
It's a big black wall!
مجرّد جدار أسود
No, it's not! That's...
لا، ليس كذلك
What is it then?!
ماذا يكون إذًا؟
I-I-I-It's...
...إ-إ-إنه
It's a whale!
!إنه حوت
Wh-Wh-What are we g-gonna do?!
!ما-ما-ماذا سنفعل؟
We should fight it!
أعلينا مواجهته؟
Are you crazy?! How are we gonna fight that?!
!كفاك مزاحًا! كيف لنا أن نواجهه؟
B-B-But, i-i-it's blocking our way!
!لـ-لـ-لكنّه يعترض طريقنا
What are we gonna do?!
ماذا سنفعل؟
Hold on a sec!
!تمهّلوا لحظة
If it looks like a wall from this close, where are its eyes?!
إن بدا كجدار من هذه المسافة... فأين عيناه؟
That's right! Maybe it hasn't noticed us yet!
صحيح، لعلّه لم يلحظنا بعد
Either way, we're about to crash into it!
!نحن قاب قوسين من الارتطام به
Hey! There's an opening on the left!
مهلًا! بإمكاننا العبور يسارًا
Port! Hard to port!
!الميسرة! إلى الميسرة
But the whipstaff is broken!
لكن الدفة مكسورة
Well, figure something out! I'll help!
!تَصَرَّف
Oh, yeah!
لحظة
I've got an idea!
راودتني فكرة
Luffy...?
لوفي؟
Hey, what are you doing?!
مهلًا، ما الذي تنوي فعله؟
This isn't working!
!لا فائدة
The ship won't turn!
!السفينة لا تستدير
Dammit!
!تبًّا
Don't give up!
!لا تستسلموا
Is this it...?!
!أحانت نهايتنا؟
The cannon?!
!مدفع؟
Alright! Did it stop?
جيد، هل توقفنا؟
We're screwed...
...هذا الأسوأ
Yeah, this is it...
...سنهلك
My special seat!
!مقعدي المفضل
Let's...
...لـ
Let's book it while we still can!
!لنهرب من هنا قبل فوات الأوان
What the heck is going on?!
!ما الذي يحدث هنا؟
Is it so big that it didn't even feel it?!
أمِن ضخامته لم يلاحظ؟
Or is it just slow?!
أم لعلّه بطيء؟
Who cares?! Let's get the hell out of here!
!من يدري؟ لنهرب بسرعة
My ears!
!أذناي تؤلمانني
Paddle! Just keep paddling!
جدف، جدف فحسب
We have to get away from it!
علينا الابتعاد عنه
Luffy...?
لوفي؟
You!
!أنت
What the hell did you do to my special seat?!
!ما الذي فعلته بمقعدي المفضل؟
– You dumbass!
!مغفل
How was that, huh?! Bring it on, you bastard!
ما رأيك بها؟ أرِني ما لديك أيها الوغد
– Shut up already, you idiot!
!اصمت أيها الأحمق
Wh-What?
مـ-ماذا؟
Luffy!
!لوفي
I'm not gonna die!
!لن أموت
What am I gonna do?
ماذا أفعل؟
They all got eaten...
!التهمهم جميعًا
Hey, you! Spit them out! Give everyone back!
!أنت! ابصقهم وأعدهم لي
Spit them out already! Listen to me!
!ابصقهم، ألم أقل لك أن تُعدهم؟
You–
...أيّها الـ
You... You jerk!
!أيّها... أيّها الوغد
Are you diving?! Stop it!
!أستغوص؟! توقف
Hey! I said stop! Hey!
!اسمعني! قلتُ لك توقف! انتظر
Please, stop! Give my friends back!
!انتظر رجاءً! أعد لي رفاقي
Hey!
!أنت
Stop it already!
!قلتُ لك توقف
We were just about to go on an adventure!
،كنّا سنخوض مغامرات عديدة معًا
I can't lose them!
!إنهم أعزاء على قلبي
Give them back!
!أعدهم
So, what do you think?
ماذا... تظنون؟
What do I think...?
ماذا أظن؟
What should I think?
فيم عسايَ أن أُفكر؟
H-H-H-H-How...?
...كـ-كـ-كـ-كيف
We were definitely swallowed by that whale...
إنني واثقٌ بأنّ الحوت ابتلعنا
Is this a dream?
أهذا حلم؟
Yeah, it's gotta be a dream.
نعم، على الأرجح أنه حلم
Then, how do you explain that island and house?
فكيف تُفسِّر تلك الجزيرة وذلك البيت؟
Hallucinations.
لا بد أننا نُهلوس
So, that's also...?
!وهذا أيضًا؟
– It's an imperial squid!
!حبّار ملكيّ عملاق
Looks like someone lives there.
يبدو أن أحدًا يسكن هناك
Let's hope they're human.
عسى أن يكون بشريًا
I've had enough. I wanna go home.
اكتفيت، أريد العودة للمنزل
Luffy's gone, too... What's gonna happen to us?
حتى لوفي اختفى، ماذا سيحلّ بنا؟
You're right! Where's Luffy?!
على ذكرك هذا، أين لوفي؟
What the heck is all this?
ما هذا؟
Why is there a door to a hallway inside a whale?
لماذا هنالك باب وممّر داخل حوتٍ؟
A ship...
...سفينة
Sh-Sh-Should we f-fire the cannon at that island?!
هـ-هـ-هـ-هل نطلق على تلك الجزيرة؟
No, hold on a sec...
...لا، انتظر لحظة
Someone's coming out...
...خرج أحدٌ